LAURA HERNÁNDEZ

Toronto, Ontario · 4372607544 **Laura.cata.hernandez08@gmail.com**

I am a hardworking, reliable team member accustomed to taking on challenging tasks. Experienced in office management with a solid background in administrative support and team leadership. Quick learner with good computer abilities. I can work calmly and effectively in fast-paced, high-volume environments to proactively address tense situations with diplomatic communication and emotional intelligence.

EXPERIENCE

NOV 2021 - SEP 2022

TRILINGUAL CUSTOMER SERVICE SUPERVISOR, TELEPERFORMANCE - REDBUBBLE.

Used databases and software programs to obtain and provide information regarding team performance. (I had up to 12 people on my team)

Supervised, monitored, and coached team members to provide feedback and address fallacies on key performance indicators to accomplish organizational goals.

Addressed escalated customer complaints to provide accurate solutions and ensure customer satisfaction.

Conducted hiring assessments and interviews, to evaluate language proficiency levels for English and French.

Managed to keep a peaceful work environment and a highly motivated team with constant support and encouragement.

MAR 2020 - NOV2021

MEDICAL INTERPRETER, TELEPERFORMANCE - LANGUAGE LINE SOLUTIONS.

Interpreted Spanish speeches to English in real-time to facilitate understanding between doctors and their low English proficiency patients.

Recognized for providing accurate, complete, and verbatim renditions, keeping the context, style, and meaning of the original message; Ensuring effective communication.

Gained experience in providing both written and oral translation between parties from various social and economic backgrounds, in different environments like hospitals, jails, 911 calls, banks, and insurance companies, among others.

SEP 2019 - MAR 2020

CUSTOMER SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE, SITEL – INSTACART.

Answered inbound calls to greet and assist customers with various needs, providing efficient solutions to complaints and inquiries.

Met productivity and quality targets while having an excellent customer satisfaction rate.

Handled escalated callers with great communication skills to reach positive outcomes.

Provided floor support for new hires, assisting on how to deal with unusual cases, and training agents on how to use the tools at their disposal to improve their performance and overall customer service skills.

FEB 2016 - OCT 2016

SOCIAL SERVICE, NUEVA ZELANDIA SCHOOL.

Worked as an English teacher at a low-income primary school on a weekly basis.

Prepared engaging lectures for kids and organized classroom spaces to cultivate a creative and fun environment for a satisfactory learning experience.

Improved my assertive communication level with young audiences and practiced my tutoring skills.

EDUCATION

NOV 2017

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA, NEW ENGLAND SCHOOL

SEP 2022 – EXPECTED TO GRADUATE ON 2024
SOFTWARE ENGINEERING TECHNICIAN, CENTENNIAL COLLEGE

SKILLS

- Emotional intelligence
- Responsible
- Committed
- **LANGUAGES**
 - Spanish, Native
 - **English**, Bilingual
 - French, Fluent

- Organized, Proactive and Efficient.
- Computer proficiency.
- Problem-solving abilities.